<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Stress Chill Map</string>
    <string name="version">1</string>

    <string name="preferences">edu.ucla.cens.stresschill.preferences</string>
    <string name="prefs">edu.ucla.cens.stresschill.preferences</string>
    <string name="surveyuploadstarted">Surveys are being uploaded.</string>
    <string name="surveyuploadstopped">Surveys are not being uploaded.</string>

    <string name="baseurl">http://stresschill.appspot.com</string>
    <string name="loginurl">http://stresschill.appspot.com/_ah/login</string>
    <string name="surveyuploadurl">"http://stresschill.appspot.com/upload_survey"</string>
	<string name="map_point_summary">"http://stresschill.appspot.com/get_point_summary"</string>
    <string name="map_full_point">"http://stresschill.appspot.com/get_a_point"</string>
    <string name="register_user">"http://stresschill.appspot.com/confirm_user"</string>

    <string name="question_00">"I am tagging this place now because of..."</string>
    <string name="question_01">"My personal interactions here and now"</string>
    <string name="question_02">"My sense of this place here and now"</string>
    <string name="question_03">"How I feel about the amount of time I spend here"</string>
    <string name="question_04">"The reason why I do something here"</string>
    <string name="question_05">"The physical condition of something here"</string>
    <string name="question_06">"My health and safety here and now"</string>
    <string name="question_07">"Memory/thought/feeling I had here"</string>

    <string name="about_content">
    StressChill is a participatory sensing campaign geared towards identifying, describing and mapping the things you find stressing or relaxing in the places you spend your time everyday.\n\n

    With this Android application you can view a map of the things participants find affect them as well as upload your own observations.\n\n

    The goal of this application is to map the things in your environment that you think need attention or to share the places you find relaxing with everyone else.</string>
    <string name="instructions_content">
    Before you start collecting data you will need to register a new account. This can be done from the main login menu (you will need an internet connection to do this).\n\n

    Upon successful registration you will be redirected to the login menu. If you want your credentials to be remembered for next time then check the checkbox on the page.\n\n

    From the home page you can navigate to either collect samples or view results. The collect option lets you take a picture, select a stress/chill value with a slider, and choose the category that describes your take on the picture content.\n\n

    The view results option brings up a map with the 50 most recent data points in your area. To see the full information on a point just tap it lightly once and then long press it until you feel the vibration.\n\n

    From all of the pages you can press the menu button to navigate between pages.</string>
</resources>
